[ Music ]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Good morning everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家早上好
And thank you for joining our
谢谢大家来参加
session.
我们的会议
My name is David Lui, and I'm
我是 David Lui
thrilled to be back here at WWDC
我很高兴能回到 WWDC
to share with you all the new
与你们分享 AR Quick Look 中
and exciting features in AR
所有令人兴奋的新功能
Last year, with iOS 12, we
去年在 iOS12 中
introduced AR Quick Look, which
我们推出了 AR Quick Look
set the foundation and provided
它奠定了基础
a great single-model AR
并提供了一个很棒的
previewing experience.
单一型号 AR 预览体验
We made it really easy to
我们使用基于物理的渲染
experience 3D content in your
以沉浸式和逼真的方法
world in an immersive and
就非常容易体验
realistic way using physically
你的世界中的 3D 内容
AR Quick Look is built in as
AR Quick Look 作为
part of iOS and is available on
iOS 的一部分内置
the web and in many applications
可在网页和许多 App
like messages and Apple News.
（如消息和 Apple News）中使用
We gave a session last year
我们去年举办了一个会议
where you could learn more about
你可以在其中了解有关
how to integrate AR Quick Look
如何将 AR Quick Look 集成
into your application and
到你的 App 和网页
website along with how to create
以及如何为其创建
great-looking content for it.
精美内容的更多信息
So, in this session, we'll go
因此在本次会议中
over our integration with
我们将介绍与 Reality Composer 的集成
Reality Composer and how AR
以及 AR Quick Look
Quick Look views the produced
如何查看制作的内容
content, improvements to the
改进视觉渲染
visual rendering, and experience
以及在 AR Quick Look 中的体验
within AR Quick Look for greater
以获得更大的
realism and content immersion.
真实感和内容沉浸感
Along with how to support all
除了如何在网络上
these new features on the web
支持所有这些新功能
including customizing the
包括为你的 App
preview and experience for your
自定义预览和体验
applications, and lastly, our
最后我们增强了
enhanced integration with retail
与零售的一体化
with support for call to action
支持号召性用语
and Apple Pay.
和 Apple Pay
So, earlier in the week, we
因此本周早些时候
talked about Reality Kit and
我们讨论了 RealityKit
Reality Composer, our new macOS
这是我们用于简单基于
and iOS tool for simple AR-based
AR 的内容创建的
content creation, where we can
我们可以通过 App 的活动
quickly create really amazing,
快速创建非常精彩
rich content with activity for
并丰富的内容
You can take all that same rich
你可以使用所有相同的丰富内容
content and share them through
并通过各种 App 共享它们
which can be viewed in AR Quick
所有这些都可以在
Look.
AR Quick Look 中查看
It's a really great way to
通过简单地共享 3D 模型文件
easily realize these new
这是一种非常好的方式
interactive experiences and view
可以轻松实现这些
them in a feature-rich
新的交互式体验
environment all by simply
并在功能丰富的环境中
sharing the 3D model file.
查看它们
And we really mean feature rich.
真的是功能丰富
In support of Reality Kit and
为了支持 RealityKit
Reality Composer, we added new
我们为 AR Quick Look
rendering effects to AR Quick
添加了新的渲染效果
Look like dynamic ray-traced
如动态光线跟踪阴影
shadows and people occlusion to
和人物遮挡
help improve the realism of 3D
以帮助改善在你世界中的
content placed in your world.
3D 内容的真实感
We've also added a lot more
我们还添加了更多功能
capabilities, like multimodel
例如多模型支持
support and a built-in animation
和内置动画扫描器
scrubber that not only enhances
不仅可以增强 AR 体验
the AR experience but gives you
还可以让你更好地
more control over the content.
控制内容
Adopting AR Quick Look is the
采用 AR Quick Look
easiest way to take advantage of
是利用所有这些新功能的
all these new features, to bring
最简单方法
an amazing AR experience to any
可以为任何 App 或网页
application or website and seek
带来惊人的增强现实体验
content as if it was actually
并让你像真的在那里
there with you.
寻找内容一样
So, let's get started.
那我们就开始吧
AR Quick Look is built around
AR Quick Look 是围绕 USDZ 建造的
Today, people create content for
今天人们用他们喜欢的
AR Quick Look using their
3D 建模软件为
and exporting that scene as a
并将该场景导出为 USDZ 文件
You can then view that content
然后你可以在
in AR Quick Look where you can
AR Quick Look 中查看该内容
push the object into your world
在这里你可以将物体推到你的世界去看
to view it.
你可以获取相同的 USDZ 文件
and import it into Reality
并将其导入 Reality Composer
Composer where you can add new
你可以在其中添加
behaviors and interactivity that
新的行为和交互性
all gets packaged up in our new
所有这些都以我们的
reality file format.
新现实文件格式打包
AR Quick Look supports viewing
AR Quick Look 支持查看
these new reality files and is a
这些新的现实文件
great place to play with these
是玩这些体验的好地方
For many users, AR Quick Look is
对许多用户而言 AR Quick Look 是
the destination to explore and
探索 3D 内容
interact with 3D content as
并与之互动的目的地
people share these models from
因为人们在许多 App 中
one device to another across
将这些模型从一个设备
many applications.
共享到另一个设备
Scenes are the fundamental
场景是现实文件的
building blocks of reality
基本构建块
A Reality Composer scene
Reality Composer 场景
contains a specified anchor
包含指定的锚类型
type, such as a horizontal or
例如水平或面放置
face placement, and one or more
以及放置在场景中的
objects placed in the scene.
一个或多个对象
These objects can contain any
这些对象可以
combination of interactive
包含交互行为
behaviors, captivating audio,
迷人音频和逼真物理的
and realistic physics.
任意组合
Together, this produces a really
合在一起 这产生了
compelling stand-alone AR
一个真实引人注目的
experience represented as a
独立 AR 体验
Reality file.
表现为 Reality 文件
So, let's take a closer look at
那让我们仔细看看
some of these properties.
其中的一些属性
Every scene has an anchor type,
每个场景都有一个锚类型
which describes how the model
它描述了模型应该如何
should be placed in the world.
放置在世界中
Last year, AR Quick Look
去年 AR Quick Look
supported horizontal anchors
支持水平锚
like tables, floors.
如桌子和地板
And this year, we've added
今年我们增加了
support for vertical surfaces
对垂直表面的支持
like walls as well as faces and
如墙壁以及面部
known 2D images in your
和环境中已知的 2D 图像
So, let's describe each of these
那我们来详细描述
in detail.
其中的每一个
Horizontal and vertical anchors
水平和垂直锚固件
are found in everyday settings
可在日常环境中找到
such as tables and floors.
例如桌子和地板
Since it is so common, objects
由于它很常见
are placed on the first detected
物体被放置在第一个检测到的平面上
plane, and we make it really
我们可以很容易地
easy to go between different
在不同的表面之间移动
surfaces, just like dragging the
就像将模型
model from one surface to
从一个表面拖到另一个表面一样
Rotation gestures differ
旋转手势根据
depending on whether the object
物体是在水平表面
is on a horizontal surface or a
还是垂直表面上而不同
And this behavior applies for
此行为适用于
both reality files and USDZ
现实文件和 USDZ 文件
So, let me show you how to place
那么 让我告诉你如何
this picture frame on the wall
从水平表面开始
starting from a horizontal
将这个相框放在墙上
I'll push the frame onto this
我将相框推到这张桌子上
table, and you can then tap and
然后你可以点击
drag the model over to the couch
并将模型拖到沙发上
and position it onto the wall.
并将其直接放在墙上
You can also start looking
你也可以直接开始寻找
directly [applause]-- thank you.
[掌声] 谢谢
directly at the wall and pushing
在墙壁上查看
the content from your device.
并从设备中推内容
It's a really seamless way to go
这是一种真正无缝的
between planes in order to
平面之间的方式
anchor your content in the world
按照你的意愿将
as you would like.
你的内容锚定在世界中
You can also anchor virtual
你还可以将与虚拟的内容
content to real-world objects
锚定到可以移动的
that can move.
真实世界物体
Like putting on eyeglasses on
就像戴上眼镜一样
For these type of experiences,
对于这些类型的体验
AR Quick Look automatically
AR Quick Look 会自动
turns on the front camera and
打开前置摄像头
anchors the content based off of
并根据相对于
how it's authored relative to
脸部中心创作的内容
the center of your face.
来锚定内容
Face occlusion geometry from
AR Quick Look 中
ARKit is used in AR Quick Look
使用来自 ARKit 的面部遮挡几何物
to realistically obscure the
来逼真地遮挡
object position on your face so
脸部上的物体位置
that they will intersect and
使它们相交
break the illusion.
并打破幻觉
Once anchored, scale and rotate
一旦锚定 缩放和旋转手势
gestures are disabled to ring
将被禁用
true to their authored size and
以响应其创作的大小
correctly positioned to your
并正确定位到你脸上
You can also take selfies with
你也可以在 AR Quick Look 中
your friends when trying on the
使用同一幅眼镜
same pair of glasses in AR Quick
与朋友一起拍照
Look and with ARKit 3 this year,
今年也可以使用 ARKit 3
there's support for up to three
最多支持三张脸
This experience is only
此体验仅适用于
available on devices with a
带有前置源深感摄像头的设备
And for other devices, the
对于其他设备
anchor is treated as if it was a
锚被视为水平锚
So here are some examples of my
这儿有一些
friends trying on different
我朋友尝试
accessories, such as a
不同配件的例子
masquerade mask, propeller
例如假面舞会面具
beanie, and this great-looking
螺旋桨帽以及
mustache in AR Quick Look.
AR Quick Look 中这个漂亮的小胡子
This makes the content more
这使得内容
animated and really feel like
更具动画效果
it's part of you since it's
并真正感觉它是你的一部分
interacting with using your
因为它与你的脸相互作用
It's a really great way to
这是一种非常好的方式
express yourself and play with
来表达自己并
these models in a brand-new way.
以全新的方式来玩这些模型
AR Quick Look uses the front
如果有单面锚
camera if there is a single face
AR Quick Look 会使用前置摄像头
If there are any other scenes,
如果还有其他任何场景
then AR Quick Look will fall
那么 AR Quick Look
back treating this as a
将会视其为
horizontal anchor experience.
水平锚点体验
So, for example, say you have
因此 例如
two face anchor scenes offered
假设你在 Reality Composer 中
in Reality Composer like I have
有两个面部锚点场景
on the left-hand side.
就像我左侧那样
So there are two different
那就有两种
styles of glasses.
不同风格的眼镜
When previewed in AR Quick Look
当在右侧的 AR Quick Look 中预览时
on the right-hand side, these
这些眼镜将作为
glasses will be placed into the
水平体验
world as a horizontal experience
放置在世界中
so you can compare them side by
所以你可以将它们并排比较
Another type of dynamic anchor
另一种动态锚点是图像锚点
virtual content can track and
其中虚拟内容可以追踪
follow a real-world image.
并追随真实世界的图像
In AR Quick Look, we want users
在 AR Quick Look 中
to be able to preview the scene
我们希望用户能够在
in the world without having
不访问物理图像的情况下
access to the physical image.
预览世界中的场景
So, if no anchor is detected, AR
因此如果未检测到锚点
Quick Look will directly place
AR Quick Look 将直接
it on the first plane that it
把其放置在找到的第一个平面上
And later, when it detects the
然后当它检测到
specified anchor, it will
指定的锚点时
magically move over and attach
它会神奇地移动并附加到
to the real-world image.
真实世界的图像上
And finally, if the anchor
最后如果锚点消失
disappears, then the scene will
那么场景将重新
reattach to the last plane that
连接到它找到的
it found.
最后一个平面
One thing to note is that
需要注意的一个点是
gestures like scale and rotate
禁用缩放和
are disabled.
旋转等手势
And like fixed anchors, the
和固定锚一样
content remains true to its
内容仍然适用于
authored size.
其创造的大小
So, let's take a look at this
让我们来看看
toy rocket model I've authored
在 Reality Composer 中作为
in Reality Composer as an image
图像锚点体验创造的
anchor experience.
这种玩具火箭模型
You can see how the content is
你可以看到内容如何
anchored to the real-world image
锚定到真实世界的图像
and follows each and every
并跟随每个移动
movement whether translate or
无论是平移还是旋转
We really encourage people to
我们真的鼓励人们
engage with the virtual content
参与虚拟内容
and really move around since
并真正走动
this is an AR experience.
因为这是一种 AR 体验
This means directly moving the
这意味着直接将
anchor closer to you, to
锚点移近你
illustrate change in scale, or
以说明比例的变化
rotating the image anchor to
或旋转图像锚点
view the scene from different
以从不同的角度查看场景
Now that you've anchored content
现在你已将内容
into your world, you can add
锚定到你的世界中
behaviors to bring interactivity
你可以添加行为以为你的场景
to your scene.
带来交互性
Behaviors are comprised of a
行为由触发器
trigger and one or more actions,
和一个或多个动作组成
and these are all defined in the
这些动作都在 Reality Composer 的
bottom behaviors panel in
底部行为面板中定义
Reality Composer, where we can
我们可以在其中
attach any combination of
附加触发器和动作序列
triggers and action sequences.
的任意组合
This is a really great way to
这是在用户和
provide more interactivity
虚拟内容之间提供
between the user and the virtual
更多交互性并
content and create a more
创建更身临其境
immersive and engaging user
且引人入胜的用户体验
experience.
的好方法
So there's a variety of triggers
因此 RealityKit 中
and actions defined in Reality
定义的各种触发器和动作
Kit that's exposed in Reality
都在 Reality Composer 中公开
Composer, and these are all
这些都在 AR Quick Look 中
natively supported in AR Quick
得到了本机支持
You can take a Tap trigger and
你可以使用 Tap 触发器
attach it to your bike object
并将其连接到你的自行车
where on tap the bike will
在这上面自行车将被拆卸
disassemble, revealing all the
显示所有单独的
individual parts and components,
零件和组件
and this is all done by the Move
这一切都由 Move 动作完成
You can also attach a Proximity
你还可以将邻近触发器
trigger to a boom box where you
连接到可以获得的音箱
can get, when you get close to
当你靠近它时
it, music starts playing that I
音乐开始播放
can jam to.
我决定的音乐
One thing to note is that AR
需要注意的一点是
Quick Look does not support
AR Quick Look 不支持
custom app actions.
自定义 App 操作
There's so many things you can
你可以使用此功能
make with this, and to learn
做很多事情
more about behaviors and how to
要了解有关行为
create interactive AR
以及如何创建交互式
experiences, check out the
增强 AR 体验的更多信息
Building AR Experiences with
请查看今年的使用
Reality Composer session from
Reality Composer 构建 AR 体验会议
So, all of these new features I
因此我描述的
described are all driven from
所有这些新功能都来自
this new Reality File.
这个新的 Reality File
Reality File is a self-contained
Reality File 是一种独立的格式
format that contains multiple
包含多个具有
scenes with any number of
任意数量对象的场景
objects, along with anchoring
以及锚定类型信息
type information, like whether
例如内容是
the content should be placed on
应放置在
a vertical wall or on a person's
垂直的墙上还是放在人脸上
face and interactivity data with
以及交互性数据
behaviors like tap triggers and
如点击触发器和音频
audio actions for realistic and
等实现和互动
interact AR experience.
AR 体验的行为
Reality files work hand in hand
Reality files 与 USDZ 密切配合
with USDZ, and USDZ is the
USDZ 是在网络或
perfect format for sharing and
App 中共享
publishing individual 3D models
和发布单个 3D 模型
on the web or in your app for
以在 AR 中使用的完美格式
And if you want to use these
如果你想使用
USDZ models you've created over
多年来创建的这些 USDZ 模型
the years, to make interactive
为了进行交互式 AR 体验
AR experiences, you can combine
你可以将它们
them in Reality Composer and
组合在 Reality Composer 中
export out a reality file.
并导出实际文件
Either format can be viewed in
这两种格式都可以在
AR Quick Look on iOS 13.
iOS 13 的 AR Quick Look 中查看
Now, I'd like to invite my
现在我想邀请
colleague, Jerry, to give you a
我的同事 Jerry 为你们提供
demo with these new experiences.
这些新体验的演示 Jerry
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, David.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 David
Good morning everyone.
各位早上好
Today I am very excited to show
我今天很高兴向你们
you previewing Reality Files
展示在 AR Quick Look 中
inside AR Quick Look.
预览 Reality Files
Now, yesterday at the Building
昨天在构建
AR Experiences with Reality
AR 体验和 Reality Composer 会议上
Composer, my friend Powell
我的朋友 Powell
created a quick lesson
创建了一节快速课程
illustrating different seasons
说明地球上不同的季节
on Earth, and he sent me a copy.
他给我发了一份副本
So let's go ahead and view that
让我们继续看看 AR Quick Look
Now, as you may recall, this
你现在可能还记得
entire experience is driven
整个体验都是通过
through scene start triggers.
场景启动触发器来实现的
For example, the moon, it
例如月球
triggers the moon to rotate
它触发月球
around the Earth and the Earth
围绕地球旋转
to rotate around the sun.
地球又围绕太阳旋转
As the Earth circles the sun,
当地球环绕太阳时
the appropriate season appears.
出现合适的季节
And this is created using weight
这是在显示动作后
action followed by a show
使用重量动作创建的
And after a slight delay, the
稍微延迟后
sign disappears using a hide
使用隐藏动作标志消失
Now, you may have noticed that
你现在可能已经注意到
no matter where I look, the sign
无论我在哪里
is always oriented towards me,
标志总是朝向我
and this is achieved by using a
这是通过使用看这个动作实现的
So, that's a quick overview of
所以快速概述
how easy it is to preview
预览 Reality Files
Reality Files, such as this
非常容易
short lesson inside AR Quick
例如 AR Quick 中这个
Look.
简短的课程
And now, I have another demo,
为此我这还有另一个演示
and for this, we're going to
我们将围绕太阳系
take a road trip around the
进行一次公路旅行
So, in the same session, my
所以在同一场会议上
friend Avi created a project
我的朋友 Avi 创建了一个
showing three celestial bodies,
展示三个天体的项目
the moon, the Earth, and the
有月亮 地球和太阳
I've expanded upon that to add
我对此进行了扩展
some more features to show you
增加了一些功能
different behaviors in action.
以向你们展示不同的行为
So let's take a look.
我们来看看吧
So the most obvious starting
我们旅程中
point of our journey is of
最明显的起点肯定是地球
But unfortunately we cannot get
但不幸的是我们无法
to space inside a car.
进入汽车内部的空间
We need something with a more
我们需要一些功能
powerful engine.
更强大的引擎
I think I have an idea.
我想我有个主意
Notice that I can see what
请注意通过看上面的文本
triggers I can interact with by
我可以看到可与之
looking at the above text.
交互的触发器
For example, here I can see move
例如在这里我可以看到
closer to activate.
接近激活
So there must be a proximity
所以必须有接近触发器
Let's go ahead and take a closer
让我们继续
look.
仔细看看 哦 这是火箭
Perfect for going to space.
非常适合去太空
Notice that I, there's a tap
请注意 我这里有个水龙头触发器
trigger here, so I'm going to go
所以我要继续
ahead and launch the rocket.
发射火箭
And we have lift off.
接着我们起飞了
So now let's set a course for
现在让我们来为月球设定路线
And let's try to stick to that
让我们试着
landing.
坚持着落 搞定了
Oh, look, there's a sign here.
哦 看 这有个标志
Well, good thing we took the
还好我们坐的是火箭
rocket, not the car.
不是车
So the thing about space is that
所以关于太空的问题
it is hard to view the sizes of
是很难看到天体的大小
celestial bodies because the
因为它们的尺寸太大
sizes are so hard it's hard to
而难以掌握
grasp.
但是我们可以通过 AR 的帮助
illustrate this with the help
轻松地说明这一点
So, I'm going to tap here and
所以我要点击这里
fly up and out of here.
然后从这里飞出去
And this time, let's go up
这次我们再往上走一点
higher so that we can take an
这样可以对
overview look of the moon, the
月球 地球和太阳有个
Earth, and the sun.
全面的了解
And I'll tap on the sun to get a
我会轻拍太阳来获得
better sense.
更好的感觉
Whoa. And as you can see, the
哇 正如你所见
sun is absolutely enormous
与地球的大小相比
compared to the size of the
太阳绝对是巨大的
Too bad the distances are not to
可惜的是距离没有
scale, otherwise it might
按比例缩放
actually be quite warm in this
要不然这个房间可能会非常暖和
So that's a quick look at how
这是一个快速查看
easy it is to view authored
如何容易地查看
content inside Reality, to view
在 Reality 中编写的内容
rich content authored using
以查看使用 Reality Composer
Reality Composer and viewed
并在 AR Quick Look 中
inside AR Quick Look.
查看丰富的内容
And we absolutely cannot wait to
我们是真的迫不及待地
see what kinds of content that
想看看你能
you can create.
创造出什么样的内容
So, now, let's talk about the
现在我们来谈谈
visual improvements of AR Quick
AR Quick Look 的视觉改进
One of the main goals of AR
AR Quick Look 的
Quick Look is to create a
主要目标之一是创建
believable AR experience, and to
可信的 AR 体验
achieve that, it is important to
为实现这一目标
understand and take into account
了解并考虑用户的
the surrounding environment of
周围环境非常重要
This year, we added a variety of
今年我们添加了
new rendering effects to make
各种新的渲染效果
the content look as if it is
使内容看起来就像它
truly part of the world.
真的是世界的一部分
let's go into some more details,
让我们看看更多的细节
starting off with real-time
从实时阴影开始
Last year, AR Quick Look
去年 AR Quick Look
rendered shadows to make virtual
渲染了阴影
content look as if was part of
使虚拟内容看起来
the world.
像是世界的一部分
This year, we made shadows
今年我们制作了动态阴影
dynamic and rendered in real
并实时渲染
So now shadows can follow your
所以现在阴影可以跟随你的内容
content as if it was part of the
就像它是世界的一部分
world, and this helps bring your
这有助于把你的动画内容
animated content to life.
带到生活中
By default, projective shadows
默认情况下使用投影阴影
are used as it provides a good
因为它可以很好地
approximation for how shadows
逼近阴影
look like in the real world.
在现实世界中的样子
And on higher-end devices, like
在像 iPhone XS 这样的高端设备上
iPhone 10S, AR Quick Look will
AR Quick Look 将采用
use a ray-traced technique,
光线追踪技术
which produces physically
可以产生
correct shadows and looks even
物理上正确的阴影
better.
看起来甚至更好
One key difference between
光线跟踪阴影
ray-traced shadows and
和投影之间的一个关键区别
projective is that ray-traced
是光线跟踪技术产生
technique produces softer
更柔和的阴影
shadows and is especially great
尤其适用于
for objects with fine contact
具有良好接触点的物体
Now, we've made great strides in
现在我们在优化方面
terms of optimizations to enable
取得了很大进展
AR Quick Look to perform
使 AR Quick Look 能够在
real-time ray-tracing of dynamic
移动设备上执行
scenes, all on a mobile device.
动态的实时光线追踪
If you're interested in learning
如果你有兴趣了解
more about ray-traced shadows, I
有关光线跟踪阴影的更多信息
recommend checking out the
我建议你今天晚些时候
Ray-tracing with Metal session
在 11 点查看
later today at 11.
Ray-tracing with Metal 会议
And since dynamic shadows are
由于动态阴影是实时渲染在
rendered in real time on all
所有支持 ARKit 的设备上的
ARKit supported devices, you do
因此你不需要
not need to bake in shadows as
将阴影作为模型的一部分
Another new visual effect is
另一个新的视觉效果
cameral noise.
是相机噪点
In low light situations, you
在光线较暗的情况下
might notice noise in your video
你可能会注意到视频中的噪点
because there just isn't enough
因为摄像机
light captured by the camera
捕捉到的光线可能不够
Since virtual objects are
由于虚拟对象
rendered on top of the camera
在相机源上呈现
feed, they will remain free of
因此他们将不受构件的影响
artifacts, making your content
使你的内容
look out of place.
看起来不合适
Well, now, Reality Kit supports
RealityKit 支持摄像头纹理
camera grain, so the noise will
所以噪点会被
be added to the virtual content
添加到虚拟内容中
based on the amount of noise in
基于摄像头
the camera feed to create an
输入的噪点量来
effect that the robot is
创建一个机器人
actually part of the scene.
实际上是场景的一部分的效果
This is done by taking the noise
这是通过获取
texture provided by ARKit and
ARKit 提供的噪点纹理
applying that to the virtual
并将其应用于
content.
虚拟内容来完成的
Camera grain is automatically
所有支持 ARKit 的设备
enabled on all ARKit supported
都会自动启用
devices.
相机纹理
Depending on your model and the
根据你的型号和环境
environment, some colors may
有些颜色看起来
look too bright or blown out,
可能太亮或太夸张
such as the shiny marble.
比如闪亮的大理石
AR Quick Look uses HDR with tone
AR Quick Look 使用 HDR
mapping to provide a greater
和色调映射来提供
range of brightness and
更大范围的亮度和对比度
As you can see, without it, the
如你所见 没有它
marble looks too bright and out
大理石看起来
of place.
太明亮不太合适
But with HDR, it blends in with
但是有了 HDR
the environment.
它与环境融为一体
Under the hood, Reality Kit
在引擎盖下 RealityKit
allocates 16 bits per color
为每个颜色通道分配 16 位
channel, and this allows for a
这样可以通过着色器
greater range of color values to
允许更大范围的
be represented and passed
颜色值得到表示
This then gets mapped using a
然后使用自定义色调
custom tone mapping curve and
映射曲线将其映射到
rendered to the final texture.
最终纹理
HDR with tone mapping is
带有音调映射的 HDR
available on all A10X devices
可用于所有 A10X
and later.
及以上设备
Now, if you're like me who has
现在如果你像我一样
tried to grab a virtual object
试图抓住一个虚拟对象
or had people walk in front of
或者让人们走在他们前面
them, then you probably noticed
那你可能会注意到
that virtual objects are always
虚拟物体总是在它应该靠后的时候
rendered in front of people when
呈现在人们面前
it should be behind, breaking
从而打破了这种幻觉
Now, with people occlusion, you
现在在人物遮挡的情况下
can create the illusion that
你可以创造一种幻觉
someone is actually walking
好像有人真的穿过
through a collection of virtual
一堆虚拟的铁皮玩具
tin toys as if it was right
就好像它真的
there in your world.
在你的世界里一样
This uses the person
使用 ARKit 提供的
segmentation data provided by
人物分割数据
ARKit to know what part of the
来了解哪个部分
camera feed should remain drawn
应该保留
on top of the virtual content.
在虚拟内容里
People occlusion takes advantage
人物遮挡利用
of the Apple neural engine and
Apple 神经引擎
will be available on all A12
并将在所有 AI 设备和
devices and later.
更好版本上使用
Now, this is a really hard
现在 这确实一个
problem to solve, but if you're
很难解决的问题
curious to learn more, I
但是如果你想了解更多
recommended checking out the
我建议你查看
Introducing ARKit 3 session.
介绍 ARKit 3 的会议
Digital cameras can only focus
数码相机在任何时候
on a certain distance at any
只能聚焦一定的距离
Objects closer or further from
离这个距离较近或较远的物体
this distance will look out of
看起来就会失焦
Without this effect all virtual
如果没有这种效果
objects will look in focus,
所有虚拟对象
which stands out from the camera
都将处于焦点状态
feed.
要从相机中脱颖而出
Reality Kit takes the object's
RealityKit 将对象的距离
distance into account tor ender
考虑在内
it as if it was captured from
就好像它是从相机中捕获的一样
And this allows the virtual
这允许虚拟对象
object to blend in with the rest
与摄像机的其余部分进行混合
of the camera feed to make it
使其看起来
seem as if it was really there.
好像就在那里
This is available on all A12X
这适用于所有 A12X 设备
Motion blur is the phenomenon
“运动模糊”是指现实世界中
caused by real-world objects
物体的运动速度
moving faster than what the
超过相机
camera can capture, creating a
捕捉的速度
steak-like effects.
从而产生类似牛排的效果
As you can see in the freeze
正如你在此处的暂停帧中所看到的
frame here, the robot on the
当模糊运动关闭时
left does not fit with the scene
左侧的机器人不符合场景
Reality Kit applies motion blur
RealityKit 通过在两个
to the virtual content by
连续帧的纹理间
interpolating between textures
进行差值来将
of two consecutive frames, which
运动模糊应用于虚拟内容
depends on the device motion and
这取决于设备运动
the length of exposure to better
和曝光程度以更好地
match the camera feed.
匹配相机输入
You'll be able to experience
你将可以在 A12X 设备上的
this effect in AR Quick Look on
AR Quick Look 中
A12X devices.
体验此效果
We strive to bring more realism
我们努力通过这些新的渲染效果
to the virtual content with
为虚拟内容带来
these new rendering effects, but
更多的真实感
we also have to keep in mind
但我们还必须记住
that these are expensive
这些都是昂贵的操作
operations that must be done in
必须实时完成
We optimize and finetune the
我们优化和微调
rendering effects to create the
渲染效果
best experience at both
在所有的 iOS 13 设备上
realistic and performant on all
创造逼真和
iOS 13 devices.
性能的最佳体验
That's why AR Quick Look would
这就是为什么 AR Quick Look
automatically apply the best
会自动为你的设备
rendering effect for your device
应用最佳渲染效果
so that you can focus on
以便你可以专注于
creating rich content and
创造丰富的内容和体验
Now, in addition to making
现在除了让内容
content feel like it is part of
感觉它是世界的一部分之外
the world, we've also made
我们还对整个视图
enhancements to the entire view
体验进行增强
First off, AR Quick Look now
首先 AR Quick Look
launches straight into AR so
现在可以直接启动到 AR
that you can immediately see and
以便你可以立即查看
interact with virtual content in
并与你世界中的虚拟内容
your world.
进行交互
For example, you can quickly put
例如你可以快速
virtual objects on detective
把虚拟对象
planes or try on sunglasses and
放在侦查机上
take selfies.
或戴上太阳镜自拍
We've also made improvement to
我们还改进了
scene understanding for better
对场景的理解
and faster plane detection to
以便更好地
push the object directly into
进行平面检测
the world as quickly as
尽可能快地将物体
possible.
直接推向世界
We used machine learning to
我们使用机器学习
better detect walls as well as
来更好地检测墙壁
to extend the breadth of already
以及扩展以检测到的
detected planes.
平面宽度
And just like last year, AR
就像去年一样
Quick Look securely runs in a
AR Quick Look 安全地运行在
sandbox process, separate from
沙箱过程中
the host.
与主机分开
By launching straight into AR,
通过直接启动 AR
websites and apps do not have
网页和 App 无法访问
access to the camera feed or any
相机提要或任何用户活动
And here's a quick video showing
这里有一个简短的视频
how fast this can be.
展示了它的速度有多快
Going to tap on the thumbnail
点击缩略图
and place a Newton's cradle directly
把牛顿的摇篮
on the table.
直接放桌上
We've also added support for
我们还增加了
viewing multiple models through
通过嵌套的 USDZ 文件
a nested USDZ file.
查看多个模型的支持
This is a special USDZ which
这是一个特殊的 USDZ
contains metadata and a library
包含元数据
of USDZs.
和 USDZ 库
This can be useful to create
这对于创建
collections of related objects,
相关对象的集合是有用的
such as a furniture set, a
例如家具装置
shopping cart, or in this case,
购物车或在这种情况
sports equipment.
是运动装备
In AR Quick Look, all containing
在 AR Quick Look 中
USDZ files are loaded and lined
所有包含 USDZ 文件的文件
up in ascending height order,
都是按升序加载和排列的
which offers a clear method of
这为显示各种不同的模型
displaying a variety of
提供了一种清晰的方法
And these can then be
一旦它们被放置到这个世界上
manipulated independently once
并按照你的喜好排列
placed into the world and
它们就可以
arranged to your liking.
被独立地操控
There's a saying that a picture
有句话说
is worth a thousand words, and a
一张图片胜过千言万语
video is perhaps millions.
而一段视频可能价值数百万
But what about animated AR
那么动画 AR 的内容呢
Animations bring a whole new
动画给用户的体验
level to the experience, and now
带来了一个全新的层次
users can control the playback
现在用户可以控制
of animations such as
动画的回放
play/pause, rewind, skip, and
如播放/暂停 倒放 跳过
fine scrubbing.
和精细擦除
And the great thing about
观看 AR 动画内容的
viewing AR animated content is
好处在于
that users can rewatch it from
用户可以从不同的角度
different angles, allowing
重新调整它
themselves to be the director.
让自己成为导演
For USDZ models, the animation
对 USDZ 模型来说
scrubber will be shown if the
如果动画持续时间
animation duration is at least
至少为 10 秒
10 seconds.
将显示动画滑块
And for content less than that,
对于低于该值的内容
the animation scrubber will be
将隐藏动画滑块
hidden, and the entire animation
并对整个动画序列
sequence will continue to loop.
继续循环
For reality files, the animation
对 Reality 文件来说
scrubber will be shown if
如果在启动触发器上
there's a single on start
至少有一个动画动作
trigger with at least one
则将显示动画滑块
And optionally, you can attach
你可以选择
sound action so that it plays
附加声音动作
along with your animated
以便与动画内容一起播放
And here's how that would look
这就是 Reality Composer 的样子
Tapping on the behaviors panel
点击行为面板
shows this.
可以看到这一点
So, here I have a single same
我这里有一个
start trigger followed by one
相同的启动触发器
USDZ animation as well as a
后面跟着一个 USDZ 动画
sound to go along with it.
和另一个声音
Now, we have a really cool
现在我们有了一个很酷的手势
It's called levitation.
叫做悬浮
Simply swipe up with two fingers
只需用两根手指向上滑动
to levitate objects up.
即可将物体悬浮起来
For example, you can levitate
例如你可以
these balloons to decorate your
悬挂这些气球来装饰
party.
你的聚会
AR Quick Look provides a portal
AR Quick Look 为用户提供了
for users to enjoy immersive
一个享受身临其境的体验门户
experiences, but wouldn't it be
但是与其他人分享
cool to share what you see on
你在屏幕上看到的东西
the screen with other people?
不是很酷吗
Now, you can record exactly what
你可以准确地
you see such as organizing that
记录下你所看到的一切
birthday party simply by tapping
比如通过点击并按住快门按钮
and holding on the shutter
来组织生日派对
button and release when you're
并在完成后松开
Videos are automatically saved
视频会自动保存
to the photos library.
到图库里
We made improvements to macOS
我们也对 macOS Quick Look Viewer
Quick Look Viewer as well.
进行了改进
In addition to being able to
除了能够预览
preview USDZ files, it also
USDZ 文件之外
supports reality files, and
它还支持现实文件
thumbnails will be generated
并且会立即生成缩略图
right away so that you can find
以便你可以
the files faster.
更快地找到文件
It is built on top of Reality
它建立在 RealityKit 上
Kit, which uses the same
使用与 iOS
physics-based rendering as iOS,
相同的基于物理的渲染
and this provides a consistent
并为所有设备提供了
previewing experience on all
一致的预览体验
We think this will make it
我们认为这样
easier to preview author content
可以更轻松地预览作者内容
and take advantage of all the
并充分利用 Mac 上可用的
power and tools available on a
所有功能和工具
That's a quick run through of
这是 AR Quick Look
all the visual improvements and
所有视觉改进
previewing experience in AR
和预览体验的
Quick Look.
快速浏览
And now I'll hand it back to
现在我将把舞台交还给 David
David, who will talk more about
他会在网页上讲更多
the integrations on the web.
关于集成的内容
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢
Thanks Jerry.
谢谢 Jerry
So we all just saw the new
我们刚刚都看到了
features and improvements added
AR Quick Look 的
to AR Quick Look this year.
新特性和改进
So, now, let's talk about how to
现在我们来谈谈
view those experiences on the
如何在网页上查看
web.
这些体验
With iOS 12, you can view USDZ
在 iOS 12 中
files on the web through AR
你可以通过 AR Quick Look
Quick Look.
在网页上查看 USDZ 文件
For your website to support
要使你的网页支持此功能
this, simply add HTML markup and
只需添加 HTML 标记
specify the MIME type.
并指定 MIME 类型即可
This automatically adds the AR
这会自动在
badge in the top right-hand
缩略图图片的右上角
corner of your thumbnail image
添加 AR 徽章
to let users know that they can
以便用户知道他们可以
view this content in AR.
在 AR 中查看此内容
Tapping on the thumbnail will
点击缩略图
launch AR Quick Look.
将启动 AR Quick Look
This easily transforms your
这很容易把你的网页
website into a seamless AR
变成一个无缝的 AR 观看体验
viewing experience as there's no
因为没有必要
need to download any
下载任何 App
Adding support consists of two
添加支持包含两件事
The HTML markup and the MIME
HTML 标记和 MIME 类型
The first step is to add the
第一步是
HTML markup, which involves
添加 HTML 标记
adding the rel equals AR
其中包括 rel equals AR 属性
attribute to your A link
添加到 A 链接元素
element, allowing Safari to
允许 Safari 浏览器
recognize and launch AR Quick
从同一个网页识别
Look from the same webpage.
并启动 AR Quick Look
The link must contain a single
链接必须包含
child that is either an image or
一个子图像或图像元素
a picture element, and the image
并且你在锚点内
that you provide inside the
提供的图像
anchor will be used as a
将用作虚拟内容的缩略图
The second step that's needed in
Safari 浏览器要识别 AR 内容
order for Safari to recognize AR
所需的第二步是
content is to add the
在提供该内容时
appropriate MIME type when
添加适当的 MIME 类型
To add support for previewing
要添加对在网页上
USDZ files on the web, simply
预览 USDZ 文件的支持
add this MIME type for USDZ
只需为 USDZ 文件添加
files.
此 MIME 类型即可
This provides the metadata for
这为 Safari 浏览器提供了元数据
Safari to open both regular and
可以直接在
nested USDZs directly in AR
AR Quick Look 中打开
Quick Look.
常规和嵌套的 USDZ
And likewise, you would need to
同样你需要配置网页服务器
serve the appropriate headers
以提供现实文件的
for reality files.
相应标头
And adding this MIME type will
添加此 MIME 类型
open reality files within AR
将在网页上的 AR Quick Look
Quick Look from the web.
打开现实文件
In addition to downloading
除了从服务器
content from a server, you can
下载内容外
also open up AR Quick Look by
你还可以通过传入本地数据
passing in local data.
来打开 AR Quick Look
One supported format is the data
一种支持的格式是 URI
URIs, which allows developers to
它允许开发人员从
load content from a base 64
基本 64 编码的数据字符
encoded data string.
加载内容
So, for example, here's how to
例如这里是
load a USDZ file through a data
如何通过数据 URL
URL.
加载一个 USDZ 文件
Notice that you specify the same
注意在开头指定相同的
MIME type at the beginning of
MIME 类型数据字符串
the data string, and to load a
并加载一个真实文件
reality file, simply switch the
只需切换
MIME type.
MIME 类型
Not only that, you can also load
不仅如此
data through blob URLs, which
还可以通过 blob URLs 加载数据
are more efficient compared to
这比 URI 更有效
data URIs since they do not need
因为它们不需要
to be base 64 encoded.
以 64 为基数编码
The blob URL is never manually
blob URL 永远不会动手创建
created and always generated
并且通过拖放
through an API like drag and
文件上载或 URL 下载
drop, file upload, or URL
等 API 生成
We've heard from developers the
我们从开发人员那里
desire to customize a viewing
听到了在 AR Quick Look 中
experience within AR Quick Look.
定制观看体验的愿望
So, starting with iOS 13, we're
因此从 iOS 13 开始
introducing two customization
我们将引入两个自定义选项
options that you can modify to
你可以修改这些选项
tailor the viewer to best fit
使查看器最适合
your content and your
你的内容和 App
Developers can choose to disable
开发人员可以选择
scaling of virtual content for
禁用正在预览的每个模型的
each model that's being
虚拟内容缩放
previewed and also provide a
并提供规范网页
canonical webpage instead of the
而不是通过 iOS 共享表
actual 3D model that'll be
iOS 共享表
shared through the iOS
共享的实际 3D 模型
So, let's take a look at the
那我们来看看
disable content scaling option.
禁用内容缩放选项
Typically, allowing scaling for
通常允许缩放虚拟对象内容
virtual content is a great way
是预览不同大小的对象
to preview objects at different
的好方法
sizes and picking the right
并且可以选择合适的维度
dimensions to best see your
以便在你所处的环境中
content in the environment that
最好地查看你的内容
However, that's not always the
然而情况并非总是如此
case, especially when previewing
尤其是在预览家具等
objects with known fixed sizes
已知固定尺寸的对象时
For these type of products, AR
对于这些类型的产品
Quick Look makes it really easy
AR Quick Look 使用网页和
for web and app developers to
App 开发人员非常轻松地
disable content scaling so that
禁用内容扩展
users will always view the
以便用户始终
object at the correct and
以正确和预期的大小
intended size.
查看对象
So, let's see what this behavior
再让我们看看这个行为
looks like with this nice dining
在我们送给顾客的漂亮餐厅里
room set that I'm sending to
看起来是什么样子的
The set comes in a specific
该集合具有
dimension that cannot be
无法配置的特定维度
You can see as I try to scale
你可以看到
the dining table set larger or
当我试着用
smaller with our two finger
两个手指捏的首饰
pinch gesture that you're met
把餐桌设置得更大或更小时
with resistance and that the
你会遇到阻力
object scales back down to its
物体会缩小到
true real-world size.
真实世界的大小
This immediate feedback is super
这种即时反馈非常重要
important to let our customers
让我们的用户知道
know that the object cannot be
对象无法缩放
scaled and that they're intended
并且他们希望
to be viewed at this specific
以这个特定的大小来查看
For the web, the API is exposed
对于网页
directly through the URL via the
API 通过片段标识符
fragment identifier.
直接通过 URL 公开
The fragment identifier syntax
片段标识符语法
starts with a hash mark followed
以散列符号开始
by the parameter option to
后面跟着参数选项
customize the AR Quick Look
用于自定义 AR Quick Look 体验
experience, and in this case,
在本例中
this allows content scaling
允许内容缩放行为
The values to these parameters
这些参数值
are Boolean values where 0
是布尔值
represents false, and 1
其中 0 表示错误
represents true.
1 表示正确
When launched AR Quick Look
启动 AR Quick Look 时
processes the fragment
将处理片段标识符数据
identifier data and ignores any
并忽略任何无效数据
invalid data along with
以及语法未定义的
parameter names that are not
参数名称
If the original URL does not
如果原始 URL
contain a fragment string, AR
不包含片段字符串
Quick Look will launch and load
AR Quick Look 将启动
the 3D content for previewing
并加载 3D 内容
using the default behavior,
使用默认行为进行预览
which is to allow content
这是为了允许内容缩放
Going through the URL fragment
通过 URL 片段标识符
identifier allows for future
可以实现未来的定制选项
enhancements to the 3D content
并增强 3D 内容预览体验
previewing experience, as more
因为 AR Quick Look
features get added to AR Quick
添加了更多的功能
Another customization option
我们添加的
that we added is the ability to
另一个自定义选项是
enable sharing the canonical
能够共享规范
webpage URL.
网页 URL
When challenged and sharing just
当挑战和共享
3D model file is the lack of
3D 模型文件时
context for where that model
缺乏上下文的模型
came from.
是从哪里来
I know my colleague Jerry is in
我知道我的同事 Jerry
the market for a new dining
正在市场上买一张新的餐桌
table, so if I send him an
所以如果我把他的 iMessage
iMessage to previous 3D model,
寄给以前的 3D 模型
he has no idea where to buy it
他根本不知道在哪里买
let alone how much the set even
更不用说要花多少钱了
For retail products, it's better
对于零售产品
to share the link to the product
最好分享产品并说明
description page.
页面的链接
And by sharing a product link
通过共享产品链接
instead of a 3D model file
而不是 3D 模型文件本身
itself, people can go to the
人们可以访问源代码
source and get not only more
不仅可以获取更多信息
information but the most
还可以获得
up-to-date information about the
相关产品的最新信息
And on iOS 13, AR Quick Look
在 iOS 13 上
will automatically share the URL
AR Quick Look 将自动共享
of the originating website for
3D 内容的原始网页的 URL
the 3D content and applications
App 可以选择
can choose to continue sharing
继续共享
that 3D model or to provide a
该 3D 模型或提供链接
This is great to get more
这非常适合获取更多信息
information and learn more about
并了解有关内容的更多信息
Now let's take a look at this
现在来看看
behavior in Safari.
Safari 浏览器中的这种行为
Here, I'm viewing the guitar
在这里 我正在从
from the AR Quick Look gallery.
AR Quick Look 画廊 观看吉他
As I tap on the share button,
当我点击分享按钮时
you'll see that were now sharing
你会看到我们正在
a reference back to the gallery
分享一个指向画廊网页的参考
website.
在 Apple News 中
automatically sharing the source
我们也会通过 iOS 共享表
news article as well through the
自动共享源新闻文章
This is great for shareability
这对于可共享性非常有用
as we pass 3D models around and
因为我们传递 3D 模型
for viewing in AR with even more
并在 AR 中查看
contextual information.
更多的上下文信息
You can also integrate AR Quick
你还可以将 AR Quick Look
Look into your iOS applications.
集成到 iOS App 中
It's really easy to integrate
它非常容易集成
and get started with viewing 3D
并开始观看 3D 内容
content and placing them into
并将其放入世界各地
Since AR Quick Look is built
由于采用了内置 AR Quick Look
into the OS adopting it gives
的操作系统
users a familiar, yet consistent
因此可为用户提供熟悉
previewing experience.
且一致的预览体验
You have full control over the
你可以完全控制
view controller frame and
视图控制器框架
presentation of AR Quick Look so
和 AR Quick Look 的呈现
you can put it inline with the
这样你就可以把它
rest of your app content or
内连到你的 App 的其他内容中
present it full screen for the
或者全屏呈现
best experience.
以获得最好的体验
AR Quick Look is built on top of
AR Quick Look 构建在
the Quick Look framework to
Quick Look 框架之上
preview and present AR content.
用于预览和显示 AR 内容
So the same customization
因此通过我们的新 API
options that are on the web are
你的 App 也可以使用
also available for your apps
网络上的相同自定义选项
To do so, use the new AR Quick
为此请使用 ARKit 框架中
Look preview item class defined
定义的新 AR Quick Look
in the ARKit framework, which
预览该类
conforms to the QL previewItem.
也符合 QL 预览项
Simply conform to the
只需遵循
QLPreviewController data source
QLPreviewController 数据源协议
protocol and return an instance
并返回 AR QL
of an AR QL preview item.
预览项的实例
To create one, pass in the file
要创建一个
URL of the 3D content that you
请传入要查看的
wish to view.
3D 内容的文件 URL
And now, you can optionally
现在你可以选择
customize and provide the
自定义并提供
canonical website URL use of
规范网页 URL
sharing within AR Quick Look and
在 AR Quick Look 中的共享使用
whether to allow content scaling
以及是否允许
of the virtual content, all
虚拟内容的内容扩展
similar to the web fragment
所有这些都与网页片段
identifier method.
标识符方法类似
This provides a consistent
这为网页和 iOS App
developer and API story for both
提供了一致的开发人员
web and iOS applications.
和 API 故事
We have a new documentation and
我们有一个新的文档和资源
resources where you can learn
你可以在其中了解
more about the APIs that we've
有关我们所涵盖的
covered along with details on
API 的更多信息
how to enable AR Quick Look in
以及如何在你的 App 和网页中
your application and website.
启用 AR Quick Look 的详细信息
So, check out this link, which
因此请查看链接
can be found on the developer
该链接可在开发人员门户网页上找到
Augmented reality is a really
增强现实是一种非常强大的
powerful way to visualize
可视化家具的方式
furniture and see how they fit
可以看到它们如何
within your space.
使用你的空间
So, I'll be showing you how to
所以我要向你展示如何
decorate a kid's bedroom with
用这六件物品装饰
these six items.
一个孩子的卧室
So, as you can see here, there
正如你在这看到的
are two picture frames, a
有两个相框
basket, a nightstand, a bed, and
一个篮子 一个床头柜 一张床
a bookshelf.
和一个书架
And all of these object are
所有这些对象都打包在
packaged together in a single
一个嵌套的
nested USDZ file.
USDZ 文件中
So let's get started moving this
让我们开始移动这张床
You can see how I'm able to
你可以看到
freely move the bed that's
我如何能够自由地将这个
contained in this multiple model
多模型文件中包含的床
file independently to my desired
独立移动到我在房间中
location in the room.
所需的位置
Let's go ahead and grab the
让我们继续并抓住
picture frames, that's on the
左边的相框
left, and move them closer to
把它移到离我们更近的地方
With two fingers, you can see
使用两根手指
that we support multimodel
你可以看到我们支持
translation, leveraging the
多模式转换
This is great for quickly moving
这对于快速移动世界
objects around in the world.
各地的物体非常有用
I will now touch and drag my
我现在将触摸并拖动
favorite picture from the floor
我最喜欢的图片
and anchor it so that it sits
并将其固定在
right above the bed.
床的正上方
This is all possible now because
这一切现在都是可能的
by default AR Quick Look detects
因为在默认情况下
and supports placing objects on
AR Quick Look 检测
both horizontal and vertical
并支持将对象放置在水平面
surfaces.
和垂直表面
Now let's figure the best place
现在让我们找出放置书架
to put my bookshelf.
的最佳位置
I'll grab the bookshelf and
我会先把书架
first place it onto the wall.
放在墙上
Now, I really need to compare
我现在真的需要比较一下
where the best spot for it is,
它们的最佳位置
so let's place it back onto the
那先把它放回地板上
So now I'm thinking, I want as
我现在在想
much floor space for the kid as
我想给孩子们尽可能多的空间
they grow up and as they collect
让他们长大
more items.
收集更多的东西
So let's keep it onto the wall
我们把它挂在墙上
since it really matches the
因为它和相框的设置
setting of the picture frame and
以及我其余的布局很匹配
I'm able to quickly make these
我能够快速做出这些决定
decisions and see what objects
并通过 AR Quick Look 中的
look like in my room with the
新支持快速做出
new support in AR Quick Look for
我房间中的物体
easily moving between horizontal
以便在水平和垂直表面之间
and vertical surfaces.
轻松移动
So, let's tidy up the rest of
我们通过移动剩下的物体
this scene by moving the
来整理这个场景的其余部分
remaining objects, which is the
也就是篮子
basket, and over to the right
然后移到书架
near the bookshelf.
附近的右边
I'll also do the same thing with
我也会用床头柜和相框
the nightstand and a picture
做同样的事情
frame but move it to the left
但是是把它移到床的右边
And as Jerry mentioned, there's
正如 Jerry 提到的
a new levity gesture, and this
这是一种新的轻浮手势
is extremely powerful for not
它不仅能
only seeing the underside of the
看到物体的底部
objects but also lifting the
还能把物体举起来
So I'll go ahead and lift the
所以我要把相框放到
picture frame to be slightly
略高于床头柜的地方
above the nightstand and move it
然后移动它
so that it's positioned just on
使其位于支架底部
Lastly, I'll rotate the frame so
最后我将旋转框架
it's angled towards the bed for
使其朝床倾斜的角度
a nice finishing touch.
为一个好的画龙点睛之笔
And now, let's take a look at
现在让我们来看看
the final shot of the kid's
我们刚刚拍摄的孩子
bedroom scene that we've just
卧室场景的最后一张照片
This looks absolutely incredible
这看起来绝对不可思议
as a prime example of a retail
作为一个零售体验的主要例子
experience that can be enabled
可在 AR Quick Look 中启用
But you might be thinking, I
但你可能会想
really wish there was an easy
我真希望有个简单的方法
way for me to buy this after
让我在自己的空间
seeing this in my own space.
看到这个以后买这个
And you weren't alone in
而且你不是唯一这么想的人
We've learned that over the last
我们从零售商那里了解到
year from retailers that when
在过去的一年里
customers see their products in
当顾客在自己的空间里
their own space, they have
看到自己的产品时
significantly more confidence in
他们对自己的购买
their purchase, which is great
有了更大的信心
for customers and great for
这对顾客和企业都有好处
So, this year, we are adding a
因此今年我们增加了
support for a customizable call
对 AR Quick Look 中
to action in AR Quick Look
可定制的号召行动的支持
including direct support for
包括对 Apple Pay 的直接支持
With Apple Pay support directly
在 AR Quick Look 中
in AR Quick Look, users can
直接支持 Apple Pay
purchase the actual objects that
用户只需点击一下就可
they just previewed in the world
购买他们刚刚在世界上预览过的
with just a single tap.
实际物品
So, what does this actually look
那这到底是什么样子呢？
like?
在 AR Quick Look 的底部
at the bottom of AR Quick Look
有一个全新的视图
with two fields, a title and a
其中有两个字段
subtitle that you can customize
一个标题一个副标题
separately to match your
你可以单独自定义以匹配
workflow.
你的工作流
The title can describe what it
标题可以描述用户正在
is that the user is looking at
购买的内容
to buy and you can use a
你可以使用
subtitle field to include the
字幕字段来包含
price and product description.
价格和产品描述
Underneath the text field is a
文本字段下方
reference to the canonical web
是对规范网页域名的饮用
domain name to show you where
以显示可以找到
the product can be found.
产品的位置在右侧
provide your own call to action,
你可以提供自己的号召应用语
such as active cart and checkout
例如有效购物车和结账
along with using any Apple Pay
以及使用具有不同
button with varying different
风格的任何 Apple Pay 按钮
styles to best fit and match
以最适合和匹配
your shopping workflow.
你的购物工作流
So this great feature will be
因此这一伟大的功能
available later this fall, and
将在今年秋季晚些时候推出
we are excited to share that
我们很高兴分享一下
Warby Parker will be offering
一旦 Apple Pay 支持
virtual try-on in their website
和 AR Quick Look
once Apple Pay support and AR
在今年晚些时候推出
Quick Look is available later
Warby Parker 将在他们的网页上提供虚拟试用
Warby Parker was the first to
Warby Parker 是第一个
offer virtual try-on in their
在他们的 App 中提供
app, and we're excited with the
虚拟试用的人
new updates to AR Quick Look and
我们对 AR Quick Look
iOS 13 they will be extending
和 iOS 13 的新更新感到兴奋
their virtual try-on to their
他们讲把虚拟试用拓展到
website.
他们的网页
We can't wait to see how other
我们迫不及待地想看看
merchants integrate this into
其他商家如何将其整合到
their retail workflow.
零售工作流程中
Now, a majority of these models
现在我们在主题演讲
that we've seen from the keynote
和本次会议中看到的
and this session can be found on
大多数模型都可以
our updated AR Quick Look
我们更新的 AR Quick Look
gallery page.
库的页面上找到
Here, you'll find a range of
在这里你可以找到一系列
static and animated models that
可以玩的静态和动态模型
you can play with, and we'll be
我们很快就会添加现实文件
So, if you have iOS 13 on the
因此如果你在设备上
device, visit this gallery page,
安装了 iOS 13
tap on a 3D model, and give them
点按 3D 模型
a try.
然后尝试一下
And also, if you didn't get the
此外如果你没有机会亲自体验
Pro or the Pro Display XDR in
会议早些时候的
person from earlier in the
Mac Pro 或 Pro Display XDR
conference, don't fret.
不用担心
You can view these products in
你可以在 AR Quick Look 中
AR Quick Look and see what they
查看这些产品
look like in your workspace.
并查看它们在工作区中的外观
The models can be found on their
这些模型可以在各自的
respective product pages.
产品页面上找到
A Python script to create these
用于创建这些
nested USDZ files will be
嵌套 USDZ 文件的
available soon on the AR Quick
Python 脚本将很快在 USDZ
Look gallery page under the USDZ
工具下的 AR Quick Look
tools section.
库页面上提供
So, in summary, we've added a
总而言之
ton of capabilities to AR Quick
我们今年为 AR Quick Look
Look this year to provide and
增加了大量功能
even more compelling and
以提供更具吸引力和可信度的体验
believable experience, to view
以便在现实世界中
AR content in the real world.
查看增强现实内容
This started with supporting
这开始于在 Reality Composer
reality files, authored in
中支持的现实文件
Reality Composer, where we're
我们能够反映
able to reflect the richness
现实工具包
that reality kit provides, like
提供的丰富性
more anchor types, such as Face
例如更多锚类型
and Real World images and
例如面部和真实世界图像
interactive content behaviors
以及通过使用触发器
through the use of triggers and
和动作的交互式内容行为
We've made the content belong
我们使用景深
with the world with new
运动模糊
rendering effects like depth of
和人物遮挡等
field, motion blur, and people
新的渲染效果使内容
occlusion.
属于世界
We also enhance the viewing
我们还通过新的
experience with new levity
率性手势和内置动画
gestures and built-in animation
扫描增强了
scrubber to allow you to have
观看体验
better control over the content
使你可以更好地控制内容
and its animation sequence.
及动画序列
We've introduced a new API on
我们在网页和 iOS 上
both the web and iOS to allow
引入了一个新的 API
developers to better customize
以允许开发人员更好地为工作流
their previewing experience for
定制他们的预览体验
And lastly, there's better
最后更好的零售整合
retail integration with support
对 Apple Pay 的支持
for Apple Pay and call to
以及对即将
actions that are coming real
到来的行动的呼吁
To learn more and get more
要了解更多关于
information about the topics
本次会议主题的信息
covered in this session, check
请访问本次会议的网页
We also have a lab later today
我们今天上午 11 点
at 11 AM.
还有一个实验室
So please stop buy and bring any
所以请停止购买并提出
questions you have about AR
有关 AR Quick Look 的任何回答
Thank you, and enjoy the rest of
谢谢大家 请享受接下来的的会议
[ Applause ]
[掌声]